Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 10. Administrative Files, 1945-2005
    - Investment Review Statement, 1987 (Box 448, Folder 16)
    - Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology
      - Acquisition, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 448, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 672, Folder 5)
    - Joint Sponsored CME Activities, 1985-1990 (Box 461, Folder 14)
    - Journal Vouchers
      - 1981 (Box 448, Folder 18-19)
      - 1982 (Box 438)
    - Kellogg-Psyllium Bulletin, 1990 (Box 672, Folder 5)
    - Leader. Educator. Advocate., 1999 (Box 503, Folder 7)
    - Leadership Directory, 2001 (Box 491, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Directory, 2003-2004 (Box 698, Folder 1)
    - Learning Resource Center, Catalog of Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 456, Folder 26)
    - Logos, undated (Box 448, Folder 21)
    - Logo Designs, Proposals, 1983 (Box 448, Folder 22)
    - Luce Press Clippings, Impact Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 456, Folder 27-28)
    - Managed Care and Allergy and Immunology Practice, 2001 (Box 705, Folder 4)
    - Marketing Needs Assessment, 2000 (Box 524, Folder 24)
    - Marketing Proposals
      - 1983 (Box 448, Folder 23)
      - Public Communications, Inc., 1986 (Box 448, Folder 24)
    - Mascot Proposal, undated (Box 448, Folder 25)
    - Media Audience Impressions Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - Media Kit
      - 1998 (Box 683, Folder 7)
      - 1999 (Box 428, Folder 10)
      - 2001 (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Media Roundtable Luncheon, January 2000 (Box 517, Folder 27)
    - Medical Service Center, Inc. vs. AAAI, et. al
      - Correspondence and Supporting Documents, 1983-1990 (Box 457, Folder 1)
      - Court Papers, 1989 (Box 457, Folder 2-3)
    - Member Services Catalog, 1989 (Box 448, Folder 26)
    - Membership
      - Change of Status
        - 1987-1993 (Box 448, Folder 29)
        - 1988-2000 (Box 665, Folder 3)
      - Counts, 1988-1999 (Box 665, Folder 2)
      - Directory
        - 1945-1965 (Box 338, Folder 1-12)
        - 1967-1975 (Box 482, Folder 1-5)
        - 1977-1983 (Box 339, Folder 1-3)
        - 1985 (Box 483, Folder 1)
        - 1987 (Box 483, Folder 2)
        - 1990-1993 (Box 340, Folder 1-4)
        - 1995 (Box 489, Folder 2-3)
        - 1997 (Box 483, Folder 3-4)
        - 2000 (Box 341, Folder 1-2)
        - 2002 (Box 488, Folder 3-4)
        - 2004-2005 (Box 705, Folder 5)
        - Codes and Descriptions, undated (Box 457, Folder 5)
      - Packet, undated (Box 428, Folder 11)
      - Renewal Acknowledgements, 2005 (Box 534, Folder 2)
      - Statistics, 1989 (Box 705, Folder 6)
      - Survey
        - Analytical Report, 1996 (Box 520, Folder 33)
        - Analytical Report, 1999 (Box 474, Folder 12)
        - Analytical Report, 2000 (Box 474, Folder 9)
        - Final Report, 2002 (Box 665, Folder 4)
    - Mosby Publishing
      - Correspondence, 1944-1993 (Box 448, Folder 31-34)
      - Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology Contract, 1995-1998 (Box 672, Folder 6)
      - Statement of Income from Publication of The Journal of Allergy, 1950-1974, 1979, 1983-1987 (Box 448, Folder 35-37)
    - Multiple Chemical Sensitivities Bibliography, 1993 (Binder 35)
    - National Allergy Bureau
      - Clips, 2000 (Box 504, Folder 1-3)
      - Fall Media Campaign, 2000 (Box 543, Folder 33)
      - Media Coverage, 1999 (Box 517, Folder 19-21)
      - Promotional Material, undated (Box 446, Folder 32)
      - Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 446, Folder 33)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, Corticosteroids & Cataracts, July 1997 (Box 672, Folder 7)
    - News Releases and Membership Communications
      - 1996-1997 (Box 457, Folder 7-8)
      - 1998 (Box 517, Folder 29)
      - 1999 (Box 517, Folder 22-23)
      - 2000-2003 (Box 698, Folder 3-6)
    - Nominations, 1993, undated (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - North American Precis Service(NAPS), Clippings, 1999 (Box 503, Folder 12)
    - Opportunities for Involvement, Brochure, undated (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Pediatric Asthma Guide, Media Coverage, 1999-2000 (Box 503, Folder 11)
    - Pediatric Asthma Initiative (Merck), 1997 (Box 683, Folder 8)
    - Pediatric Asthma: Promoting Best Practice, 1998 & undated (Box 540, Folder 12)
    - Pollen and Spore Reports
      - 1963-1980 (Box 336, Folder 1-6)
      - 1981-1984, 1987-1992 (Box 337, Folder 1-5)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 449, Folder 8-9)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 489, Folder 4-5)
    - Position Statements
      - Adverse Effects and Complications of Treatment with Beta-Adrenergic Against Drugs, 1995 (Box 371, Folder 1)
      - Allergen Skin Testing, 1993 (Box 449, Folder 2)
      - Allergen Standardization, 1980 (Box 371, Folder 2)
      - Anaphylaxis in Schools and Other Childcare Settings, 1998 (Box 537, Folder 91)
      - Antihistamines and Managed Care: Old Versus New, 1998 (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Approval Procedure, 1997 (Box 371, Folder 4)
      - Autogenous Urine Immunization, 1976-1981 (Box 371, Folder 5)
      - Beconase, 1997 (Box 672, Folder 8)
      - Beta-2 Agonists, undated (Box 449, Folder 3)
      - Candidiasis Hypersensitivity Syndrome, undated (Box 371, Folder 6)
      - Carotid Body Excision, and Miscellaneous, 1984-1986 (Box 457, Folder 9)
      - Clinical Ecology, undated (Box 371, Folder 7)
      - Compilations
        - 1971-1999 (Box 705, Folder 7)
        - 1993 (Box 465, Folder 21)
      - Controversial Procedures, A Review of Golbert, Lowell, 1975 (Box 371, Folder 8)
      - Controversial Techniques, 1981 (Box 371, Folder 9)
      - Cytotoxic Testing, undated (Box 371, Folder 10)
      - Cytoxicity Testing, 1981 (Box 371, Folder 11)
      - Discontinuation of Hymenoptera Venom Immunotherapy, 1997-1998 (Box 371, Folder 12)
      - Double Blind Food Challenge (Proposal), 1994 (Box 449, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Allergen Avoidance in Allergic Asthma, 1998 (Box 371, Folder 13)
      - Epinephrine Injection, 1972 (Box 371, Folder 14)
      - Fluoride, Allergy to, 1971-1993 (Box 371, Folder 15)
      - Future of the Subspecialty of Allergy and Immunology, 1997 (Box 520, Folder 7)
      - Guidelines to Minimize the Risk from Systematic Reactions Caused by Immunotherapy with Allergenic Extracts, 1993 (Box 449, Folder 5)
      - Health Care Reform, 1994-1996 (Box 371, Folder 16)
      - Idiopathic Environmental Intolerance (IEI), 1998 (Box 371, Folder 17)
      - Inhaled Corticosteroids and Severe Viral Infection, 1993 (Box 457, Folder 10)
      - Latex Allergy, 1998 (Box 371, Folder 18)
      - Measurement of Circulating IgG & IgG Food Immune Complexes, 1987 (Box 371, Folder 19)
      - Measurement of Specific & Non-Specific IgG4, 1988 (Box 371, Folder 20)
      - Measurement of Specific and Non-Specific IgG4 Levels as Diagnostic and Prognostic Tests for Clinical Allergy, 1994 (Box 449, Folder 6)
      - Methods of Practice Regarding Lab Procedures, 1978 (Box 371, Folder 21)
      - Oral Ingestion Food Challenge, 1996 (Box 371, Folder 22)
      - Participation in Other Meetings, 1977, 1980 (Box 371, Folder 23)
      - Practice Parameters on Consultation with an Asthma Specialist, 1995 (Box 371, Folder 24)
      - Provocative & Neutralization Testing, 1981 (Box 371, Folder 26)
      - Provocative Testing, Sublingual, 1981 (Box 371, Folder 25)
      - RAST for Diagnosis of Specific Allergens Responsible for IgE Mediated Diseases, 1982 (Box 449, Folder 7)
      - Rast & IgG Tests in Practice, 1980 (Box 372, Folder 1)
      - Rast Marketing, 1980 (Box 372, Folder 2)
      - Remote Practice of Allergy Position, 1985 (Box 372, Folder 3)
      - Remote Practice of Allergy, undated (Box 372, Folder 4)
      - Resuscitative Equipment, 1981 (Box 372, Folder 5)
      - Role of Allergists in Hospitals, 1982 (Box 372, Folder 6)
      - Role of the Allergist/Immunologist as a Subspecialist, 1996-1997 (Box 372, Folder 7)
      - Safety and Appropriate Use of Salmeterol in the Treatment of Asthma, 1995-1996 (Box 372, Folder 8)
      - Safety of Allergenic Immunotherapy, 1988 (Box 372, Folder 9)
      - Skin Test Proficiency, 1992-1993 (Box 372, Folder 10)
      - Suggested Approaches for Recruitment of Asthmatics into Clinical Trials, 1995-1997 (Box 372, Folder 11)
      - Tag-On Meetings, 1981 (Box 372, Folder 12)
      - Tartrazine, 1977 (Box 372, Folder 13)
      - Theophylline Use in Asthma, 1995 (Box 372, Folder 14)
      - Treatment of Systemic Reactions, 1985 (Box 372, Folder 15)
      - Use of Epinephrine in Treatment of Anaphylaxis, 1997 (Box 372, Folder 16)
      - Use of Standardized Allergen Extracts, 1997 (Box 372, Folder 17)
      - Voluntary Health Organizations, 1976 (Box 372, Folder 18)
      - World Health Organization Allergen Immunotherapy: Therapeutic Vaccines for Allergic Diseases, 1998 (Box 372, Folder 19)
    - Practice Parameters for the Diagnosis and Management of Drug Allergy, Draft, 1996 (Box 449, Folder 10)
    - Practice Parameters for the Diagnosis and Treatment of Asthma
      - undated (Box 494, Folder 2)
      - Initial Draft, 1989 (Box 495, Folder 6)
    - Preparation of Needs-Based Requirements for Allergy and Immunology for the Year 2010, Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 449, Folder 11)
    - Press Conference, Fatalities Due to Anaphylactic Reactions to Foods, 2001 (Box 543, Folder 37)
    - Press Releases and News Clippings
      - 1951-1954 (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 342, Folder 2-9)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 343, Folder 1-7)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 344, Folder 1-4)
      - 1982 (Box 449, Folder 12)
      - 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 344, Folder 5-9)
      - 1987-1990 (Box 672, Folder 9-10)
      - 1996-1998 (Box 457, Folder 11-20)
      - 1996-1999 (Box 673, Folder 1)
      - 1998 (Box 458, Folder 1-2)
      - 1999 (Box 531, Folder 1-3)
    - Professional Education Continuing Medical Education Survey, 1994 (Box 526, Folder 14)
    - Professional Education Outreach Programs, 1994 (Box 543, Folder 47)
    - Proponents of Board Allergy, Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 449, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for a Legislative Monitoring System, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 11)
    - Proposal for Training and Certification in Clinical Immunology, 1990 (Box 458, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations Plan, 1996 (Box 534, Folder 33)
    - Radio Ads, 1995 (Box 673, Folder 2)
    - Reorganization, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - Reorganization Proposal, 1993 (Box 449, Folder 14)
    - Report to the Scientific Council by S. Roger Hirsch, 1975 (Box 449, Folder 15)
    - Resource Based Relative Value System, Miscellaneous, 1987-1990 (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - Sample Books
      - 1976-1977 (Box 346, Folder 3-4)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 346, Folder 5-6)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 347, Folder 1-6)
      - 1981-1985 (Box 348, Folder 1-7)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 349, Folder 1-4)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
      - 1987 (Box 349, Folder 5-7)
      - 1988-1990 (Box 350, Folder 1-5)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 351, Folder 1-4)
    - Samter Journalism Award, 2001-2002 (Box 543, Folder 54)
    - Schering, Beconase Study, 1996-1997 (Box 705, Folder 8)
      Folder is restricted. Contact archivist for details.
    - Schering-AAAAI Discussion Meeting, June 1999 (Box 705, Folder 9)
    - Schmidt-Dunlap vs. AAAI, et. al.
      - Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 449, Folder 16-17)
      - Court Papers, 1987-1990 (Box 449, Folder 18-19)
    - Schulz, William A., Lectureship, 1959-1973 (Box 449, Folder 20)
    - Scientific and Educational Projects Budget Proposal
      - 1989-1991 (Box 463, Folder 17)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 449, Folder 21)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 490, Folder 2-3)
    - Seldane and Hismanol, 1992 (Box 673, Folder 3)
    - Speakers Bureau
      - Information, undated (Box 449, Folder 22)
    - Specialty Choices Among Second Year Medicine and Pediatric Residents, Center for Health Workforce Studies, 2002 (Box 543, Folder 46)
    - Spectrum Communications, 1996-1998 (Box 673, Folder 4)
    - Sponsorship Directory
      - 1998-2000 (Box 459, Folder 2)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 322, Folder 14)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities, Booklet, 2000-2002 (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - Staff and Housing Budget, 1993 (Box 449, Folder 23)
    - Staff Inservice, 1999 (Box 540, Folder 11)
    - Staff Liaison Responsibilities, 1999 (Box 449, Folder 24)
    - Staff Retreat
      - 1997, 2000 (Box 449, Folder 25-26)
      - 1998 (Box 526, Folder 28)
    - Steps to Joint Sponsorship and Recognition for Continuing Medical Education (CME) Programs, undated (Box 534, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Plan, 1997-2000 (Box 512, Folder 8)
    - Strategic Plan Brochures, 1997-2005 (Box 428, Folder 19)
    - Supply, Demand and Distribution of Allergists and Immunologists in the United States: A Descriptive Analysis, Report 1, 1999 (Box 474, Folder 10)
    - Survey - National Allergy and Immunology Manpower Survey, 1994-1990-1987 data analysis (Box 673, Folder 5)
    - Survey of Physicians, Patients and Pharmacists, 1985 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Survey of Practice of Allergy & Clinical Immunology, summary report, 1984 (Box 673, Folder 6)
    - Survey of Residency/Fellowship Training Programs in Allergy and Immunology, 1990 (Box 449, Folder 27)
    - Task Force for Marketing Allergists
      - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 449, Folder 28)
      - Proposals, 1986 (Box 449, Folder 29)
    - Task Force on Allergic Disorders, Media Report, 1999 (Box 504, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, 1950, 1962, 1976-1991 (Box 449, Folder 30)
    - Ted Klein and Company, Reports, 1971 (Box 449, Folder 31)
    - Theophylline Media Crisis, October 1990 (Box 673, Folder 7)
    - Theophylline, Trial Lawyers, 1990 (Box 673, Folder 8)
    - Time Magazine
      - Article, 1988 (Box 673, Folder 9)
      - Proposal, 1987 (Box 673, Folder 10)
    - Trademark Applications, 1990-1991 (Box 449, Folder 32)
    - Understanding and Managing Asthma: Update for the Managed Care Environment, Evaluation Results, 1995-1996 (Box 465, Folder 13)
    - Web Site
      - 1996, 1999 (Box 673, Folder 11-12)
      - Brochure, 2005 (Box 540, Folder 38)
      - Hard Copy, 1998 (Box 449, Folder 33)
      - Informational Mailing, 1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 540, Folder 3)
      - Re-Design, Correspondence, 1996, 1998 (Box 463, Folder 18)
    - Welcome (new member) Packet
      - 1991, 1993, 1994 (Box 449, Folder 34-36)
      - 1995-2002, 2004 (Box 666, Folder 1-10)
    - World Asthma Meeting
      - Barcelona, 1997-1998 (Box 665, Folder 6)
      - Chicago, 2001 (Box 665, Folder 7)
  - 10A. Administrative Forms, 1983-2006
    Forms including surveys, order forms, questionnaires and applications can be found in this series.
    - Advertising Space Contract, 1997, 2000 (Box 447, Folder 49)
    - Asthma and Allergy Advocate, 1986-1987 (Box 543, Folder 20)
    - Asthma Morbidity and Mortality Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 463, Folder 19)
    - Asthma Scholarship Program Application, 2000, 2004 (Box 474, Folder 11)
    - Basic and Clinical Immunology Interest Section Survey, 1996 (Box 534, Folder 23)
    - Course Examinations, 1987, 1990, 1992 (Box 475, Folder 10)
    - Disclosure Statement, undated (Box 534, Folder 17)
    - Dues Mailing Samples (forms), 1987-2004 (Box 683, Folder 4-5)
    - Educational Grant Contract, undated (Box 534, Folder 16)
    - Educational Resources Catalog, 1993 (Box 447, Folder 29)
    - Grant-In-Aid Award, Applications, 1990-1991, 2000 (Box 463, Folder 23)
    - Letterhead, 1995-1998 (Box 448, Folder 20)
    - Manpower Survey, undated (Box 463, Folder 21)
    - Marion Merrel Dow-AAAI Scholar in Allergy Award Application, 1991 (Box 463, Folder 22)
    - Membership Applications, undated (Box 448, Folder 27)
    - Membership Certificate, 1999-2000 (Box 448, Folder 28)
    - Membership Certificates, 1990s-2002 (Box 665, Folder 1)
    - Membership Directory Questionnaire, 2000-2001 (Box 457, Folder 6)
    - Membership Questionnaire, 1998 (Box 448, Folder 30)
    - Membership Survey, 2005 (Box 537, Folder 71)
    - National Resident Education Program Applications, 2001-2003 (Box 543, Folder 51)
    - President's Grant-In-Aid Award Application, 1990-1991, 2000 (Box 463, Folder 23)
    - Public Education Materials, Order Form, undated (Box 463, Folder 24)
    - Research Award in Bronchial Asthma Application, 1992 (Box 463, Folder 25)
    - Scholar in Allergy Award, Application, 1990 (Box 447, Folder 13)
    - Self-Report Form for Continuing Education, 2001-2002 (Box 474, Folder 13)
    - Sinusitis Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 463, Folder 26)
    - Strategic Training in Allergy Research (STAR) Program Application, 2006 (Box 540, Folder 41)
    - Summer Fellowship Application, 1997, 2002, undated (Box 463, Folder 27)
    - Training Program Directors Graduates Survey, 1996 (Box 463, Folder 28)
    - Training Program Directors Recruitment Issues and Problems for Academic Allergy and Immunology Centers and the Training Programs Questionnaire, undated (Box 463, Folder 29)
    - Training Program Directors Controversial Methods and Inappropriate Testing Questionnaire, undated (Box 463, Folder 30)
    - Training Program Directors Travel Grant Application, 2000, 2002 (Box 463, Folder 31)
    - Travel Grant Award Application, 1988-1991, 2002-2006 (Box 474, Folder 14)
    - Utilization of RAST Testing Questionnaire, 1983 (Box 463, Folder 32)
  - 11. Associates to the AAAAI, 1956-2005
    The Associates are spouses and friends of the members of the AAAAI. This series contain meeting minutes, press clippings, membership directories, information about scholarship programs, and fundraising activities by the Associates.
    - Annual Meeting Information, 1951-2004 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, Photographs, 1980-1999 (Box 369, Folder 1-20)
    - The Associates [Newsletter], 1986-2007 (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Asthma Scholarship Program, 2000-2004 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting Minutes
      - 1980-1988 (Box 368, Folder 2-10)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 543, Folder 23)
      - 2002 (Box 474, Folder 15)
    - Charter, 1982 (Box 712)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, 1981, 1985, 1995-1996, undated (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1981-1995, undated (Box 368, Folder 11)
    - Finances, 1981-2000 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Fund Raising Activities
      - Holiday Cards, 1983-1988 (Box 368, Folder 12)
      - Ties, Pins, and Scarves, 1983-1996 (Box 368, Folder 13)
      - Silent Auction, 2002 (Box 475, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1980-1996 (Box 367, Folder 1-12)
      - 1997-1999 (Box 682, Folder 1-2)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 543, Folder 24)
      - 2002 (Box 682, Folder 3)
    - Health Care Reform, 1990-1993 (Box 368, Folder 14)
    - History of Associates, 2001, 2004 (Box 682, Folder 4)
    - Logo Apparel Catalog, undated (Box 428, Folder 9)
    - Membership Directories, 1984-1985, 1987-1988, 1989-1990 (Box 368, Folder 15)
    - Membership Information, undated (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Membership Survey, 2000 (Box 526, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, undated, 35 mm safety film negatives (Box 3)
    - Patient Education for Asthma and Allergy Knowledge
      - 1996 (Box 682, Folder 5)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 543, Folder 43)
      - American Society of Association Executives Award, 1998 (Box 543, Folder 38)
      - Assessment, 1998 (Box 526, Folder 30)
      - Brochures, 1997-2002 (Box 447, Folder 37)
      - Program Information
        - 1998 (Box 682, Folder 7)
        - 1999 (Box 682, Folder 8)
        - 2000 (Box 474, Folder 5)
        - 2001 (Box 682, Folder 10)
      - Report 1997 (Box 682, Folder 6)
      - Report 1999 (Box 682, Folder 9)
    - President's Summary Report, 2000-2001 (Box 682, Folder 11)
    - Products Order Form, 1997 (Box 534, Folder 21)
    - Questionnaires, 1980s (Box 370, Folder 7)
    - Reports to AAAI Executive Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 370, Folder 8)
    - Romania Abstract Book Project, 1996-1997 (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Schoenkerman, Evelyn, In Memoriam, 1994 (Box 369, Folder 14)
    - Slate of Officers, 1982-2002 (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - Slides, undated, Slides (35 mm) (Box 369, Folder 21)
    - Sparks, Caroline, In Memoriam, 1997 (Box 369, Folder 18)
  - 12. Oral History Interviews of the Oral History Project for the AAAAI, 2000-2002, 44 audiocassettes
    Interviews conducted by Sarah Filzen from 2000 to 2002.
    Past presidents and prominent members of the AAAAI discuss major events and shifts in AAAAI's history, the impact that AAAAI has had on the profession, and the changing roles and perceptions of allergy in the medical field.
    Per the AAAAI Board of Directors, access to the oral histories is restricted for the lifetime of each interview subject. Researchers interested in accessing these interviews should consult the AAAAI archivist, who will work with the AAAAI office to determine if they are open for research. Researchers that have gained permission must use digital access copies for the audio records.
    - Aaronson, Donald, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, John A., 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 2)
    - Austen, Frank K., 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 3)
    - Baer, Harold, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 4)
    - Becker, Robert, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 5)
    - Bernstein, Leonard I., 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 6)
    - Buckley, Rebecca, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 7)
    - Bukantz, Samuel, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
    - Cohen, Sheldon, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 8)
    - Dworetzky, Murray, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 9)
    - Fink, Jordan, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 10)
    - Frick, Oscar, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
    - Gottlieb, Phillip, 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 11)
    - Kaplan, Allen, 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 12)
    - Levine, Macy, 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 13)
    - Lichtenstein, Lawrence, 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 14)
    - Lockey, Richard, 2002
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 15)
    - Malkiel, Saul, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 16)
    - Mathews, Kenneth, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 17)
    - McNeil, Don, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 453)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 18)
    - Norman, Phillip S., 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 19)
    - Patterson, Roy, 2000
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 454)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 20)
    - Rachelefsky, Gary, 2002
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 21)
    - Reed, Charles, 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 454)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 22)
    - Reisman, Robert E., 2001
      - Interview, 1 audiocassette (Box 541)
      - Transcript (Box 511, Folder 23)
    - Seebohm, Paul M., 2000
      - Interview, 2 audiocassettes (Box 454)